<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Things worth writing on damihl</title>
    <link>http://damihl.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Things worth writing on damihl</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 15:13:21 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damihl.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey to Getting Something Done Part 2</title>
      <link>http://damihl.github.io/posts/journey-to-getting-something-done-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 13:14:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damihl.github.io/posts/journey-to-getting-something-done-part-2/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s been two weeks since my last post in this series. In this time I have been on the edge of Not Getting Something Done again, staring into the depths of Abandoned Projects gulch. Every little bit of light that gets through the thick fog of Procrastination and Overplanning let&#39;s you get a glimpse of something long forgotten; wonderful ideas and projects, glaring back into your eyes for a second until it retreats back into the never ending darkness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey to Getting Something Done - Part 1</title>
      <link>http://damihl.github.io/posts/journey-to-getting-something-done-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 15:04:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damihl.github.io/posts/journey-to-getting-something-done-part-1/</guid>
      <description>The first thing I needed to do was define the kind of game I wanted to make within the constraints that I defined before.
 Actually the first thing I already decided beforehand was the engine that I&#39;m going to use. Obviously because this series is about getting something done I&#39;m not going to write my own one.
The game will be made in Godot, mainly because it is free, open source, easy to use and just great overall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey to Getting Something Done - Foreword</title>
      <link>http://damihl.github.io/posts/journey-to-getting-something-done-foreword/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 17:22:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damihl.github.io/posts/journey-to-getting-something-done-foreword/</guid>
      <description>I have a strong history of successfully not getting things done. In fact theres a very specific set of things that I&#39;m not getting done: Personal stuff.
Obviously I don&#39;t struggle to get things done at work, otherwise I wouldn&#39;t have a job.
It&#39;s also no problem for me to finish a box of chocolates, or binge watch an entire season of Brooklyn 99 the day it releases on Netflix. No, it&#39;s this very specific set of things that just refuse to get to a state which most people would call &amp;lsquo;Done&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>